In the last lecture, we created our own button component,
Kendi dme bileenimizi oluturduumuz son dersi sonlandr.
let's now use it in the order summary where we have two buttons.
imdi bunu iki dmeyiz olan sipari zetinde kullanalm.
First of all in that component, I'll import my own button from the UI folder, there from, not from the backdrop,
Her eyden nce bu bileen tm iinden UI klasrnden kendi dmesini ie aktarr; dme klasrnden
from the button folder, the button.js file
zemin fonksiyondan dme js dosyas.
and now, we can simply replace the default button here with my own button as we set it up to output props.
Ve varsaylan olarak, ancak yeni yl kendi dmeyle deitirebiliriz. kty ayarlarken
children, here we can simply wrap the text we want to put on the button with our own button element.
ocuk istiyor, burada kendi dme enizle dmeye koymak istediiniz metni basite sarabiliyoruz.
Now there are two properties we need to define on the button, clicked and button type,
imdi dme toplamak ve Dme trn bulmak iin ihtiya duyduumuz iki zellik var.
so let's quickly do that,
Hadi abucak balayalm.
let's start with button type maybe, for cancel I want to set button type to Danger and make sure to
Dme trn belki iptal ediciden renelim Dme trn tehlikeye atmak ve bakent
use a capital D because you need to match the name we use here in the button.css file,
D kullandnzdan emin olmak istediimden burada burada kullandmz ad C asfaltyla eletirmeliyiz.
Danger and Success,
Tehlike ve baar.
these are the two values we can use.
Bunlar kullanabileceimiz iki deerdir.
You can of course change them or add new ones
Elbette ki onlar deitirir veya yenilerini eklersin.
but these are the ones I supplied you with.
Ancak iSuppli ile baa kanlar bunlar.
So button type danger
Yani dme tipi tehlike.
and on the second one button type success, like that and of course as I said there is this
Ve ikinci bir dme tipi baar byle ve elbette dediim gibi merdiven var.
click property which it also uses, which the button component also uses.
Dme bileeninin de kulland zellik de kullann.
So we should also set up clicked,
Bu yzden de toplamay ayarlamalyz.
this will be triggered when the button is clicked and of course here we want to execute some method
Bu dme tklandnda tetiklenecek ve elbette burada sipari zet bileeninde
which since we're in the order summary component, we also have to receive here dynamically.
olduumuzdan dinamik olarak almak zorunda olduumuz baz yntemleri uygulamak istiyoruz.
Now the order summary component gets used in the burger builder component or container,
imdi zet bileen sras Bergere yapc bileen veya kabnda kullanlr.
so therefore we should pass a property to order summary or to properties actually, one which will pass
Dolaysyla bu nedenle, bir zeti veya iki zellii ieren bir mlk gemeliyiz; bu durumda, bu durumda bu
a reference in the case that we want to continue with the purchase, a reference to a method which then handles
davay ileyen bir yntemi ve davay ileyen bir ynteme bir referans satn
this case and a reference to a method which handles the case that
almaya devam etmek istiyoruz diye bavuruyu geireceiz .
we don't want to continue.
Devam etmek istemiyoruz.
We already got a method for not continuing, the purchaseCancelHandler,
Satn alma iptal ileyicisini devam ettirmemek iin zaten bir yntemimiz var.
now I will add a third method,
imdi nc bir yntem ekleyeceim.
purchaseContinueHandler.
Devam ileyicisini satn aln.
I'll also define this with this arrow function syntax and there for now I will simply throw an alert,
Bunu da bu ok fonksiyonu szdizimi ile tanmlayacam ve imdi
you continue because that is all we can do for now.
imdi yalnzca uyarlar takip etmeye devam edeceim nk imdilik tek yapabileceim bu.
Now let's pass these two methods references to the order summary and we can choose any property names
imdi, bu iki metot referansn sral zete geirelim ve istediiniz herhangi bir mlk
we want,
adn seebiliriz.
so I'll add a purchaseCanceled event here or property name where I want to execute the purchaseCancelHandler
Bu yzden Che'nin iptal edilen etkinliini burada veya mlk adn, Chase ncesi Cance Landler' yrtmek
and I'll add the purchaseContinued property which holds a reference to the
istediim yere ekleyeceim ve satn alma devam eden ileciyle ilgili bir referans tutan purchase
purchaseContinueHandler.
continue zellii ekleyeceim.
Now with that, let's implement these two, whoops, cancelled with two L's though,
imdi onunla iki tane de iptal edilen bu iki hub' hayata geirelim.
let's implement these two properties in the order summary,
Bu iki zellii sipari zetinde uygulayalm.
there we have the buttons,
Orada dmeler var.
if we click the cancel button, then we want to execute props.purchaseCancelled,
ptal dmesine tklarsanz pervanenin satn almn iptal etmek istiyoruz.
if we clicked continue button, we want to execute props.purchaseContinued was the property which holds
Che'nin devam ettirdii pervanenin idamesini istediimiz doru yntemi tutan zelliktir.
the correct method referenced then.
Eer klik devam ederse,
Let's see if that works, if we save this and we add ingredients and click order
Bakalm, eer bunu yaparsak bunun ie yarayp yaramayacana bakalm ve katk maddeleri ve tklama emri ekledik.
now, here are the buttons.
te dmeler.
If I click Cancel, it does the same as clicking the backdrop does, it dismisses the modal. If I click continue,
ptal'i tklarsam, arka plana tklayarak tklama ileminin devam etmesini tklarsam modalin tklanmasna devam eder.
I get the alert which says you continue.
Devam ettiini bildiren uyary alyorum.
Now this is the modal and this is the
imdi bu modal ve sahtekrlktr.
burger builder as far as we can build it from a build the burger side.
Burger reticisi, burger tarafn ina etmek iin yapabileceimiz kadaryla.
Later in the course, we'll also add functionality to really kind of make the purchase and store that in
saklama trnde ilevsellik de eklenecek ve gerek bir sunucuysa siparii muhtemelen ileyeceiz.
a database on a real server where we then probably would process the order if that were a real app
Kursun ilerleyen ksmlarnda, gerek bir sunucuda bir veritabannda satn alma ve
and we'll also add more pages so that the user can also see a page of the orders he placed.
Ayrca, kullanc, yerletirdii siparilerin bir sayfasn grebilmek iin daha fazla sayfa ekleyeceiz.
And of course in case you already know redux, no worries, we'll also overhaul this app with redux.
Ve elbette ki zaten okumay biliyorsanz, x endieleri Rydex'le birlikte bu uygulamay yenileyecektir.
We're not done yet though,
Yine de bitmedi.
have a look at our app,
Uygulamamza bir gz atn.
what's missing?
Ne kayp.
The toolbar, the sideDrawer and the backdrop for the sideDrawer.
Ara ubuu belirleyicisi, sitenin arka plandr.
Well at least we got the backdrop but here we still got some work to do,
En azndan zemini aldk ama yine de yapacak baz ilerimiz var.
this is what we'll focus on next.
Desire, sonra odaklanacamz ey.